cooksrecipes.com 2005-04-05

# Cooks Recipes | Privacy Policy for CooksRecipes.com

This is the website of CooksRecipes.com.

CooksRecipes.com strongly believes in a consumer's right to privacy. CooksRecipes.com does not engage in the collection, distribution, sale or use of personally identifiable information about Web Users, such as name, phone number and street address. CooksRecipes.com does not conduct individual web user "profiling".

For the Web User to CooksRecipes.com's Web page, our Web server automatically collects information on your domain type, browser used and your IP address for statistical purposes only, which is used to improve the content of our Web page and not shared with other organizations for any purpose.

With respect to cookies: We do not set any cookies.

All email addresses submitted to CooksRecipes.com in regard to our newsletter, CooksRecipes Digest, or for any other reason will be kept strictly confidential and private. You can be assured our mailing list will NEVER be shared or sold as a whole or in part.

If you supply CooksRecipes.com with your postal address on-line you will only receive the information for which you provided us your address.

Persons who supply CooksRecipes.com with their telephone numbers on-line will only receive telephone contact from us regarding the information for which you provided us your telephone number.

**Third Party Advertising**  
We use MaxOnline and other third-party advertising companies to serve ads when you visit our Web site. These companies may use information (not including your name, address, email address or telephone number) about your visits to this and other Web sites in order to provide advertisements on this site and other sites about goods and services that may be of interest to you. If you would like more information about this practice and to know your choices about not having this information used by these companies, please click here

**Third Party Cookies**  
In the course of serving advertisements to this site, our third-party advertiser may place or recognize a unique “cookie” on your browser.

For further information, please consult the privacy policies of:

If CooksRecipes.com's policy on information practices change at some time in the future, we will use only the data collected from the time of our policy change forward.

With respect to security: If and when CooksRecipes.com transfer and receive certain types of sensitive information, such as financial information, CooksRecipes.com will redirect visitors to a secure server and will notify visitors through a pop-up screen on our site.

Regarding Outside Links: This website contains links to other websites. Please be aware that CooksRecipes.com is not responsible for the privacy practices of such other websites. We encourage our users to be aware when they leave our website and to read the privacy statements of each and every website that collects personally identifiable information. This privacy statement applies solely to information collected by this website.

If you feel that this site is not following its stated information policy, you may contact The DMA's Committee on Ethical Business Practices at mgoldberger@the-dma.org, The Federal Trade Commission by phone at 202.FTC-HELP (202.382.4357) or electronically at <http://www.ftc.gov/ftc/complaint.htm>.

Contact CooksRecipes.com
